perzue.com 2019-07-29

# PRIVACY POLICY

**_Perzue's Privacy Commitment Overview_**

**_Privacy Statement_**

Perzue has created this privacy policy for [www.perzue.com](http://www.perzue.com/) (the “Web Site”) in order to demonstrate its firm commitment to privacy. (“We” or “Us”, as used in this Privacy Policy) The Privacy Statement discloses Perzue’s information gathering and dissemination practices for the information collected through only this Site and not any other web site.

By registering or by using this site, you explicitly accept, without limitation or qualification, the collection, use and transfer of the personal information provided by you in the manner described in this Policy. We strongly encourage you to read this Statement carefully before using this Site. Your use of this Site signifies that you agree with all terms of this Statement, including the way information is collected and personal information is processed, so please do not use this Site if you disagree with any part of this Policy.

**_Scope of this Policy  _**

This privacy policy applies to information that only we collect and not to any other web sites. However, the Site contains links to other web sites, which have their own privacy policies. If you on your end choose to link to those other web sites from our Site, we are not responsible and hence, our privacy policy will not comply over your actions. We do not control the practices of data use of:

(a) Employers or others who may access your information on this Site, or

(b) Third party Ad Networks and other third parties with whom we work to serve you personalized ads on our Site.

We encourage you to find out how the networks manage the privacy of your information and how to opt-out of information collected by these networks.

**_Information We Collect and Retain_**

We do not collect any personal information for simply surfing our Site in attempts of job searches or to read the content on it. However, we do collect the following information when you visit/create account on our Site.

1.  Personally Identifiable Information

We will collect personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, address, email address, telephone number, contact information, billing information, etc. when you provide it and share it with us while on this Site.

2\. Demographic Information

We will collect demographic data, such as your postal code or ZIP code, age, gender, race or ethnicity, occupation, career background and interests.

3\. Passive Collection of Non-Personal Information

We will also collect behavioural information such as IP addresses and various environmental variables.

  * The “IP address” is a number used by computers on the network to identify your computer so that data can be transmitted to you.

  * “Environmental variables” include, among other things, how you use our site, and mobile applications, the areas of our site that you visit, the services you access, information about your computer hardware and software including your geo-location, browser and operating system type, domain names, the names of the page you visit while at this Site and the internet addresses of the websites you then visit.

This information is collected for Perzue’s internal use such as to enhance website security, to identify broad demographic trends, analyse the use of resources and prevent troubleshooting problems and fraud to otherwise enhance your experience on this Site. In addition, Perzue may collect indirect information from you when you use certain third party services on our website as it is deemed necessary for the same purpose stated above. Information about third parties, such as references or contacts that you provide to us must have their express written consent to do so.

We may collect both personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information, individually or together. In each case, it will indicated on the website whether any personal or demographic data must be provided to use the requested service or not.

We do not collect sensitive personal data such as:

·    Financial information such as Bank Account details or Credit Card or Debit Card or other payment related details;

·    Physical and mental or other health conditions or medical records and history;

·    Biometric information such as finger prints, voice & facial patterns and DNA

We will not collect any other sensitive information that is confidential or sensitive by its nature. We do not store information of users like password of your e-mail account. The password of your Perzue account automatically gets saved in the our server when you create an account or register with Perzue. We do not authorize for access unless desired under any legal obligation.

We make certain information publicly available, by default, because we intend to allow you to share your information and to allow others to find you. However, you can control the visibility of your information available to others by deleting information that you do not want visible or by not providing it at all.

The public availability of any information that you post on another user’s profile or comment on another user’s post, will be subject to the other user’s privacy settings.

To enhance your experiences on our website, we may information about you from the third parties who provide it to us, to personalize the advertising that you may come across on our site or other sites with which we have a business relationship. We may share this information with our partners, but only in aggregate, for them to understand how Perzue visitors use our website. We will not disclose any information about you to any outside party except when the applicable law, rules or regulations demand it or in legal proceedings when such information is relevant.

**_Use of Cookies, Web Beacons, and Java Script  _**

We also use cookies, web beacons, and Java Script to administer our site and deliver a personalized experience. For additional detailed information on each of these, please see below.

_Cookies:_

Perzue uses "cookies" to help personalize and maximize your online experience and time online, including for storing user preferences, improving search results and ad selection, and tracking user trends.

We predominately use "session" cookies, which are not permanently stored on your hard drive. Session cookies expire after two hours of inactivity or when you close your browser. When you carry out a job search or apply online a large amount of data is processed by our system and transferred through each page of the search or application process. This information includes your job search criteria, data that identifies your resume, covering letter, the job you are applying for, your right to work in the relevant country and the results of any questionnaire you have completed as part of the online application process as well as demographic information that is not unique to you. "Session" cookies allow us to keep track of this data until you have completed your search or application. We also use cookies to identify users who have been banned from using our forums for behaviour that contradicts our terms of use and to track click streams, for load balancing and to enable you to navigate through the site using redirection pages.

You can opt-out of customized advertising by third parties by setting your browser to decline third party cookies or some browsers allow you to block cookies from a particular third party whose customized advertising you do not wish to receive.

Please note that if you opt-out of cookies by changing your browser settings, your opt-out will be saved but it may not be carried with you if you choose to use another browser or login from another computer. You should check your browser settings each time you open a new browser or login from a different computer.

Additionally, Perzue uses "Flash cookies", also known as "Local Shared Objects", to preserve video player settings and for user authentication purposes. You can adjust your settings for your Flash cookies here.

_Web Beacons:_

Perzue Web pages and the Web pages of our partners also utilize electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs, clear gifs or action tags) that allow us to collect certain information about user visits to these Web pages (including the number of users who have visited those pages), measure and improve the effectiveness of advertisements and job postings, and deliver co-branded services.

You cannot opt out or refuse web beacons because web beacons are the same as any other content request included in the recipe page. However, they can be rendered ineffective by either opting out of cookies or changing the cookie setup in your browser.

_JavaScript:_

Perzue also uses JavaScript, for example, within certain advertisements. JavaScript is a script language that enhances the functionality of websites, particularly in respect to pictures. We are not collecting any personal data via JavaScript but use it to inform employers about how many applicants have clicked on email addresses embedded in their job ads, for example. You may deactivate JavaScript via your browser settings or activate it the same way. If you disable JavaScript you will not be able to use some of the functions of the website.

**_How we use information_**

We use the information we collect about you to deliver the product and services we offer, respond to you, to operate and improve your experience on our website.

We use your information, subject to local law, after we obtain your consent to register with Perzue, manage your profile or opt in when presented with choices in the following ways:

· To use information provided to us by a third party such as your contacts or advertisers, to communicate with you through emailing you updates about our website including security or privacy updates, send newsletters, feedback forms and promotional advertisements.

· To provide your information in a searchable resume database in job postings to employer customers.

· To help your friends, contacts and potential employers find your profile and connect with you.

· To allow you to share jobs and profile information with your connections.

· To detect, investigate and prevent activities that may violate our policies to be illegal.

· To create a network to share and compare profiles, career background and experience and provide ‘Forward to a Friend’ feature.

· To generate internal reports about the working of our site.

We also provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of these types of communications. If you choose to receive these types of communications at the time of registration, but later you decide against it, you can simply log in to your ‘My Perzue’ account and edit your account profile.

We are duty bound to safeguard your information from unauthorized access or inappropriate use by third parties. However, we are not responsible for the information that you post publicly on the Site that is later used by a third party because we do not have any control over them.

We cannot ensure that all your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Commitment. Therefore, although we are committed to protecting your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications would always remain private. As a user of the Perzue, you understand and agree that you assume all responsibility and risk for your use of our website and your actions and conduct on and off our website.

**_Disclosure of Information to Others_**

We disclose the personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information to third parties in the manner below:

1.Your resume to potential employers who have posted job opportunities on the Site that may be of your interest.

2\. For delivery of services such as, hosting our web servers, analysing data, providing marketing assistance, processing payments and providing customer services to you by a third party employed by us. These companies and individuals may be located in a country whose data protection legislation is different from your country, and they will have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions. We will be responsible for them to not share your information with any other third party or use that data for any other purpose.

3.We may disclose such information to third parties only if you consent to such disclosure. For instance, if your resume is searchable then all parties with access to our searchable resume database (or copies thereof) will have access to your resume. However, if you indicate to us by configuring your profile that you want to receive information about opportunities, specific products, services then we will share your contact information to only selected third parties such as employers, data recruiters, data aggregators, marketers, etc.

4\. We supply technology, hosting, hiring management and related services to other leading companies to power recruitment areas on their Web sites (sometimes referred to as "Hosted Career Sites"). Personal and/or demographic information supplied by you in Hosted Career Sites becomes part of the Perzue database, but it is not accessible by anyone other than you, Perzue, and the company concerned without your consent. If you apply for a position through a Hosted Career Site or a co-branded site, you may be asked to provide information regarding your age, gender or race where permitted by law. However, Perzue is not responsible for the actions of such employers. We will keep all such information provided by you separate from your expression of interest in any job opportunity. Providing this information is strictly voluntary and you will not be subject to any adverse action or treatment from us if you choose not to provide this information.

5\. We will disclose information if legally required to do so or at our discretion pursuant to a request from a governmental entity or if we believe in good faith after considering your privacy interests and other factors that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect our rights or property or our affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public.

6\. We may disclose and transfer such information to a third party who acquires any or all of Perzue's business units, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In addition, in the event Perzue becomes the subject of an insolvency proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, Perzue or its liquidator, administrator, receiver or administrative receiver may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the court. You will be notified of the sale of all or a substantial portion of our business to a third party by email or through a prominent notice posted on the Sites.

**_Policy For Private Resume Database Hosting_**

We provide a platform for hosting private databases such as Hosted Databases in which these databases use certain Perzue applications for their operation. These Databases may contain personal information about individuals, including candidates for employment and existing employees of our customers. Such data may include contact details, work history, educational history, work preferences, and other data, depending on the particular customer and application at issue, and, in some instances, may include personally identifiable information. But we do not own the data in the Hosted Databases.

Perzue’s customers act as data controllers with respect to all such Hosted Databases. The data in such databases, including any such data submitted to our applications, is subject to the customer’s privacy policies. If you are a candidate for employment with one of our customers, you should refer to the customer's Terms & conditions / Privacy page on their career site to understand the terms and privacy practices that apply to your data. Moreover, if you would like to access and review your Personal Information, you should contact our customer with any such requests. We will cooperate as appropriate with requests from our customers to assist with such responses. We are not responsible for its customers' privacy policies or practices.

**_An Important note about your Resume_**

We give you the option of putting your resume in our database.

When you create or post a resume on the Site, that resume is stored in our searchable resume database in Singapore. You may control the status of your resume by setting it to private or public.

You can store your resume in our database, but not allow it to be searchable by potential employers or recruiters. Not allowing your resume to be searchable means that you can use it to apply for a job online, but employers and recruiters will not have access to search it through our resume database product.

If you set your resume as private, it is not searchable by potential employers or others with access to our resume database. You may still use your resume to apply online for a job. If you do apply online for a job, your resume will be transferred to the relevant employer, who may retain a copy of your resume or distribute it to third parties. We cannot control their use or retention of your resume information.

If you set your resume as public, but want your contact information to be confidential, your resume will be searchable by potential employers, but we will hide your contact information and current company. You must also remove your contact information from your uploaded or copy and paste text resume. You should be aware that if you have a rare skill or job title, it may still be possible for you to be identified even without your contact details being included. If you are worried about being identified, you should not include specific details by which you could be identified. If you use a confidential resume to apply to a job online, the employer to whom you send your resume will be able to view your contact information in order to contact you about your application.

We attempt to limit access to our searchable resume database to legitimate users such as paying employers, recruiters, hiring managers, head hunters and human resource professionals, as well as law enforcement and national security agencies, but cannot guarantee that other parties will not gain access to this database. We cannot control the use made of resumes by third parties who access such resumes while they are in our searchable database. You may remove your resume from our searchable database at any time; details of how to do this are given below. However, employers, recruiters and others who have paid for access to that database, as well as parties who have otherwise gained access to the database may have retained a copy of your resume in their own files or databases.

We will take reasonable steps to ensure that parties other than those mentioned above will not, without our consent, gain access to this database. However, Perzue is not responsible for the retention, use, or privacy of resumes by any third parties. We cannot control the retention, use or privacy of resumes or profiles that have been downloaded by third parties. Accordingly, you should not put sensitive information, personality profiles, or other information you would not want made public, in your resume.

If you provide us with details of a reference, it is your responsibility to ensure that the person is aware that you have forwarded his/her details and has consented in writing for you to do so.

If you use our facilities to build a resume or to post a resume in our database, then you will be providing us with personal data we will use in accordance with this Statement. Your resume must not contain sensitive data relating to your (i) racial or ethnic origin (ii) political beliefs (iii) philosophical or religious beliefs (iv) membership of a trade union or political party (v) physical or mental health or genetic makeup (vi) addictions, sexual life (vii) the commission of criminal offences or proceedings and associated penalties or fines, or (viii) any Social Security Number or national identification number.

If you set your resume as private unless you have previously sent to us your written consent that we may process your sensitive personal data, then we may take this into account if Perzue determines this to be a requirement of applicable law. If your resume does contain such data and you set your resume as public, then you agree that we may retain this information and use it in accordance with this Statement. We cannot control third parties' access to such information from our searchable database.

**_Access to personal information_**

We retain indefinitely all the information we gather about you in an effort to make your repeat use of the Web Site more efficient, practical and relevant. You can delete your resume from Perzue's online database, close your account at any time in which event we will remove all our copies of your resume and your account information from the Web Site, except for an archival copy which is not accessible on the internet. You can also edit the information you have submitted by logging into your ‘My Perzue’ account.

Before providing you with a copy of your personal information or correcting, updating or deleting such information, we reserve the right to verify and authenticate your identity and the personal information to which you have requested access. Access to or correction, updating or deletion of your personal information may be denied or limited by Perzue if it would violate another person's rights and/or as otherwise permitted by applicable law.

            If you wish to delete or close your account or account profile information altogether, please contact us at admin@perzue.com to contact us. An email will be sent to you to confirm that your personal information has been deleted (save for an archival copy which is not accessible by you or third parties on the Internet). The archival copy is retained only for as long as Perzue reasonably considers necessary for audit and record purposes. We will also retain logs, demographic, indirect, and statistical information that may relate to you but do not identify you personally. If others using our Site previously accessed your personal information, we are not able to delete the information or copies thereof from their systems.

            If you do not want your information to be processed as described by this policy, you make revoke your consent to our Privacy Policy. If you wish to do so, please admin@perzue.com (mailto: admin@perzue.com) to contact us. However, please note that if you do withdraw your consent, you may not be able to use the relevant services and your account and profile information will be deleted.

**_Online Security_**

When you provide information on our Site, you agree this information may be transferred to a Perzue database in another country.

**_Feedback_**

Perzue has areas on the Web Site where you can submit feedback. Any feedback that is submitted through this area becomes the property of Perzue. We may use this feedback at any time for any purposes, such as success stories for marketing purposes, or to contact you for further feedback on the Web Site.  

**_Children_**

We do not specifically collect information about children. Neither will we contact children under the age of 13 years. If you are concerned about your child's use of Perzue, we encourage you to use Web Filtering technology to supervise your child's access to the Web Site.

**_Changes to Privacy Statement_**

_If we decide to materially change the substance of this Privacy Statement, we will, where required, contact you via the email address that you maintain in your profile. We will also post those changes through a prominent notice on the web site so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it. Thank you for using Perzue. We are committed to providing you with the best tools and advice to help you get ahead in your career. We welcome your feedback and suggestions. Please contact us by calling or email admin@perzue.com ( _mailto: admin@perzue.com_ ) _

_Thank you for using Perzue._
